YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 3. National Administrative Office
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VI. PUBLICITY
  - Publications
    - General YWCA information
      - Membership Leaflets series, circa 1926-30 (Box 261, Folder 7-10)
      - Speakers Hand Book: 1921 Edition, 1921 (Box 261, Folder 11)
      - True Stories of the YWCA in 12 Episodes for presentation over local radio stations, 1937 (Box 261, Folder 12)
      - The YWCA: Material for Speakers, 1941 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Graphic Guidelines Manual, 1988 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Models for Action information kits, 1980-82 (Box 262, Folder 3-4)
    - Publicity
      - General guides, 1934-87 (Box 262, Folder 5)
      - As Others See Us: A Guide for Public Relations Planning in the YWCA of the USA, 1961 (Box 262, Folder 6)
      - YWCA On the Air: A Radio Publicity Handbook, circa 1942 (Box 262, Folder 7)
      - Packets
        - "Interpreting the YWCA," circa 1958 (Box 262, Folder 8)
        - Circa 1991 (Box 262, Folder 9)
        - 135th Anniversary of the YWCA, 1993 (Box 262, Folder 10)
        - YWCA Media Guide, 1994 (Box 262, Folder 11)
        - 1997 (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - Serials
      - "P.R. Update," 1981-83 (missing vols. 1, 3, 5) (Box 262, Folder 13)
      - "Communications," 1991-92 (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1936-63 (Box 262, Folder 15)
  - Reports
    - Miscellaneous, 1921-61 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Publicity Secretary, Helen A. Ballard, 1913-16 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Publicity Committee of the South Atlantic Field Committee, 1916 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Public Relations Office (Box 263)
      - 1942-47 (Box 263, Folder 4-9)
      - Monthly, Jun 1942-47 (Box 263, Folder 10)
    - Public Information Department, 1948-49 (Box 263, Folder 11)
  - Studies
    - "The Gallup Study of Public Awareness and Involvement with Non-Profit Organizations," conducted for National Board YWCA of the U.S.A., 1987 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Miriam Bedrick Marketing Research study toward developing an effective communications program, 1991 (Box 264, Folder 2)
  - Training
    - General, 1968, 1987 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Public Relations Workshop at Cluster Meetings, 1977 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - National Board Training, "Working with the media," 1994 (Box 264, Folder 5)